

# **NG KAI HONG CLEMENT**

Brisk · Creative · Open-minded

#### **ABOUT ME**

Passionate software developer with 4 years of professional experience building Objective-c and C++ desktop application. Learning the latest cutting edge development tools and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

#### Education

2005~2010	2010~2012	2013~2015	2015~2017
Salesian English School	Modern College	CCCU (AscISD)	HKUST (BEng in COMP)

# **PROJECT WORK**

- - 耆樂寶 A system for handling the photo, video and entertainment (CCCU FYP)
- E-care A platform for simplifying the process of medicine acquisition or appointment (HKUST Mobile Application Design Contest)
- FaceT An aesthetic and easy-to- use mobile app platform for enhancing women's experience in shopping for cosmetic products (HKUST FYP)

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

- 07/2012 08/2012 Station Assistant — Chandler Macleod group (HK) limited
- 07/2015 09/2015 Production Assistant — Photobition Hong Kong Limited
- Junior Mobile Application Developer (Java) Accord HK 12/2016 — 02/2017
  - Work in a team to design and develop quality mobile application
  - Deploy for the mobile application
- 06/2017 03/2021 03/2021 - Now

Software Developer — PremiumSoft CyberTech Ltd.

Senior Software Developer — PremiumSoft CyberTech Ltd.

- Develop and maintain Navicat for Linux (C++ and Qt Creator) and Mac side (Objective-c and Xcode) which is a multi-connection database development tool
- Collaborate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple. intuitive interaction and experiences

# **MY SKILL**

Photoshop

**PowerPoint** 

Word

Excel

### Programming:

# C++Java Kotlin Objective-C PHP Swift Other: Adobe XD

#### **CONTACT ME**



github.com/clementf2b



+852 9432 3416



ng2b30@hotmail.com



FLAT 04, 3/F, BLOCK 31 HENG FA CHUEN **CHAI WAN** HONG KONG